* [
    
    Login](https://www.thetradedesk.com/us/our-platform/login)

Close×

* [
    
    Login](https://www.thetradedesk.com/us/our-platform/login)

Website Privacy Policy
======================

_Last updated: November 20, 2024_  

**WHAT THIS POLICY COVERS**

**INFORMATION WE COLLECT **FROM OUR WEBSITES AND OTHER SOURCES****

**HOW WE USE THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT**

**HOW WE SHARE INFORMATION**

**EUID  
**

**COOKIES ON OUR WEBSITES**  

****CANDIDATE INFORMATION**  
**

**YOUR RIGHTS**

**INTERNATIONAL TRANSFERS**

**SECURITY AND RETENTION**

**CHANGES TO THIS POLICY**

**CONTACT US**

**WHAT THIS POLICY COVERS**

Scope. This website privacy policy covers data that The Trade Desk collects, uses and discloses from our “Websites” (namely, [www.thetradedesk.com](https://www.thetradedesk.com/us), [www.thecurrent.com](https://www.thecurrent.com/), client-facing portals, careers page ([www.careers.thetradedesk.com/jobs](https://careers.thetradedesk.com/jobs)) or any other site where this policy is displayed), and by other means, including through your contact with us.

It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your personal data or personal information (“personal data”) and your rights.

Out of Scope. This policy does not cover data that is collected, used or disclosed through the Trade Desk’s advertising technology platform or systems (the “Platform”). For more information on our privacy practices, as they relate to the Platform, please see [The Trade Desk Services Privacy Policy](https://www.thetradedesk.com/us/privacy).

This policy also does not apply to the privacy practices of other websites that are linked from our websites. The Trade Desk is not responsible for the privacy practices of these other websites. We encourage you to read the privacy policies of those websites to understand their data privacy practices.

****INFORMATION WE COLLECT **FROM OUR WEBSITES AND OTHER SOURCES******

We collect data, including personal data, such as your name, email address and phone number directly from you. For example, when you provide information through a form on our websites, when you sign up to receive communications by us, or when you apply for a role through our career pages.  
  
We also collect data through third party services for the purpose of job recruitment, such as vendor platforms that provide candidate search and data engine for sourcing and recruiting efforts, or through event management services, when you attend an event hosted or sponsored by us.  
  
Additionally, we automatically collect analytics data, such as browser type and language, access times, pages visited, and referring website addresses, and mobile data such as the mobile browser and type and model of your device. We use this data to understand how our websites are used and how to improve them.

**Analytics Data**

We may automatically collect analytics data, such as browser type and language, access times, pages visited, and referring website addresses, and mobile data such as the mobile browser and type and model of your device. We use this data to understand how our websites are used and to improve them.

****HOW WE USE THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT****

Any personal information you provide to us will only be used for the purposes for which you provided it, as disclosed at the time it was collected. For example:

* To respond to inquiries and provide requested information regarding our products and services;
* To consider you for a role which you have applied for;
* To send you marketing communications related to our products, such as our newsletter, if you are a client or have chosen to receive it.

o If you no longer wish to receive marketing email communications, you can either follow the unsubscribe link and instructions contained in the emails you receive or you can request to unsubscribe at: [Preference Center | Update email preferences](https://pages.thetradedesk.com/Preference-Center.html).

**HOW WE SHARE INFORMATION**

We may disclose data, including your personal data, to companies that provide data processing services to help us with our business activities, such as sending email communications on our behalf. These companies are authorized to use your information as necessary to provide these services to us.  

We will also disclose your information:

* As required by law, such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process,
* When we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request,
* If the Trade Desk is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, in such case you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our websites of any change in ownership or uses of your information, as well as any choices you have regarding your information, or
* With your permission, to another third party.

**UID2 and EUID**

We may use your email address to create a consistent unique identifier called an UID2 or, in Europe, a EUID. These allow us, and other participants in the UID2/EUID advertising framework, to ensure that the ads you see online are relevant and measure the effectiveness of our advertising.

You can read more about how UID2 works on [Transparentadvertising.org](https://transparentadvertising.org/).

You can read more about how EUID works, how to opt-out and your rights on the [EU Transparency website](https://www.transparentadvertising.eu/privacy).

**COOKIES ON OUR WEBSITES**

“Cookies” are data files that are stored on your browser or device and are used to remember user preferences and behaviors over time. Cookies allow us to recognize your device and remember information, such as your preferred language and other general settings. For more information about specific cookies on this site, please see our [Cookie Notice](https://www.thetradedesk.com/us/cookie-notice).  

**CANDIDATE INFORMATION**

If you are a candidate for an employment opportunity at The Trade Desk, we will process the data necessary to manage your engagement for opportunities at The Trade Desk, for example the interview process and access to The Trade Desk offices.

We may keep your profile information when you log-in to the career site using LinkedIn, apply for jobs, subscribe to job alerts or join Talent communities. See the YOUR RIGHTS section below for information on how to request your data with us.  

**YOUR RIGHTS**

Depending upon where you live, some states, countries or regions provide individuals certain legal rights with respect to the personal data organizations collect and process about them. These rights may include the right to request access, deletion, and/or correction of personal data. They may also include the right to opt out of activities that constitute “sales” or “sharing,” as such terms are defined under certain state privacy laws in the United States. These rights may be limited, for example if fulfilling your request would reveal personal information about another person or infringe the rights of a third party (including our rights) or if you ask to delete information that an organization is required to keep by law.  
  
If you reside in a state, country or region that provides individuals such rights to their personal data and would like to access, correct, or request deletion of the personal data we have about you in connection with the scope of this privacy policy, please follow the steps indicated below, depending on your relationship to us:  

* For Website visitors or general business contacts: please fill out and submit this [webform](https://privacyportal-eu.onetrust.com/webform/2abc1a63-35c5-4ef7-b11b-1c55714738b5/61b81601-fe65-4dfe-a922-e1c5a68fa8cb)
* For employment applicants through our Careers Page: fill out and submit the [TTD Applicant/Employee Privacy Request webform](https://privacyportal-eu.onetrust.com/webform/2abc1a63-35c5-4ef7-b11b-1c55714738b5/2da26cf0-fabe-431f-91a6-568f4fc5dc04).
    * Please be aware that requesting a deletion of personal data will remove your entire profile information from the career site including any active job applications. This will also remove any subscriptions you might have made on the career site.

We will ask you to verify your identity once you submit your request. Should your request be denied, we will inform you of the reasons for denial, including any relevant exceptions or exemptions we relied upon when responding to your request. We will not discriminate against you if you exercise your rights under applicable law.

**INTERNATIONAL TRANSFERS**

We operate from servers located in the United States. Laws governing the collection and use of data in the United States may not be equivalent to those in the country where you reside.  
We may transfer data from the EU or Switzerland to the US under a valid legal framework.  

**SECURITY AND RETENTION**

We retain the personal information you provide to us for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services or perform the purposes for which it was supplied. We will retain and use your personal information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

We have implemented commercially reasonable security measures, including physical, electronic and administrative safeguards, to prevent the unauthorized access to, loss, misuse, or alteration of the personal information we process.

**CHANGES TO THIS POLICY**

We may revise this policy at any time. However, if we make material changes, we will not apply them retroactively.

**CONTACT US**

If you have a concern regarding our privacy practices, please contact us via the contact details supplied below.

* Mail: The Trade Desk, Attention: Global Data Protection Officer (DPO)-Global Privacy Office, 42 N. Chestnut St., Ventura, CA 93001  
    
* Email: dpo ((at)) thetradedesk ((dot)) com

If, after reasonable efforts, you believe your concern has not been satisfactorily addressed by us, you may reach out to your local data protection authority.

* If you are in the US, our privacy practices are regulated by the Federal Trade Commission or state-specific data protection authorities;
* If you are in the EU, we recommend you contact you contact the Data Protection Authority in the Member State where you normally reside;
* If you are in the UK, we recommend you contact the UK Information Commissioner’s Office (ICO).

<<END OF POLICY>>

Let's work together. See what our platform can do for you.

Contact Us

©2024 The Trade Desk. All rights reserved.
